<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Client on Yarra Framework</title>
    <link>http://yarra-framework.org/tags/client/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Client on Yarra Framework</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yarra-framework.org/tags/client/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yarra on XA Scanners</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/running_on_xa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/running_on_xa/</guid>
      <description>Background The &amp;ldquo;Numaris X&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;XA&amp;rdquo; software, which is running on the newest MAGNETOM scanners (Vida, Sola) and on upgraded scanners (Prisma, Skyra, Aera, &amp;hellip;), introduced several security or &amp;ldquo;system hardening&amp;rdquo; mechanisms, including the Windows Kiosk mode and the requirement to enter the admin password whenever starting an application outside of SyngoMR. While it is generally good news that the security has been improved, these new protections make it difficult to use Yarra routinely because they require leaving the Kiosk mode after each system reboot and require entering the admin password repeatedly when launching the Yarra RDS or ORT client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Yarra Diagnostics</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/yarradiagnostics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/yarradiagnostics/</guid>
      <description>The Yarra Client package now comes with a new tool called Yarra Diagnostics, which helps identifying various problems that can occur on the scanner side. The tool can either be started using the Windows Explorer (by clicking the icon Diagnostics.exe) or from the ORT Client (by right-clicking on the orange Yarra logo and selecting &amp;ldquo;Diagnostics&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;).
When clicking the &amp;ldquo;Run Diagnostics&amp;rdquo; button, the tool conducts a series of tests to identify installation and configuration issues as well as collects system information that may be helpful for resolving Yarra-related problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.62</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_062/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_062/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the Yarra Client package has been released (version 0.62), which provides multiple improvements and new features:
Added support for scanner software versions XA40A and XA50A New Yarra Diagnostics tool, which analyzes various configuration issues on scanners that may impact different Yarra components (network connectivity, DNS configuration, etc) RDS: New option to buffer exported raw data on a different location than the C:\ drive, which may be needed when exporting large scans on scanners with a small hard drive Updated UI with dark-mode design, which blends better into the user interface of XA-line scanners The version is now available in the Download section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.60</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_060/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_060/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the Yarra Client package with minor improvements has been released (version 0.60).
The version is now available in the Download section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.59 with Support for XA30/XA31</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_059/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_059/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the Yarra Client package has been released (version 0.59) that adds support for the Siemens software versions XA30A and XA31A. In addition, RDS now has an option to disconnect from the network share after the update has been completed.
The version is now available in the Download section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.58</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_058/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the client package has been released (version 0.58) that adds support for the Siemens software versions XA20A and XA20B. In addition, several minor bugs have been fixed.
The version is now available in the Download section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.55</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_055/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_055/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the client package has been released (version 0.55) that now also supports the Siemens software version VE11S. Moreover, the SAC client now allows sending additional files along with the task, enabling to send, e.g., separate calibration data to the reconstruction module.
The version is now available in the Download section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client Package 0.54</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_054/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/client_054/</guid>
      <description>A new version of the Yarra Client Package has been released (version 0.54). This version offers improved support for the scanner software XA11A and XA11B.
Starting with version XA11A, Siemens has changed the Windows security policies such that even the execution of white-listed applications requries entering the password of the administrator account each time. This can be cumbersome when submitting offline-reconstruction tasks. Therefore, we added an alternative mechanism for launching the Yarra ORT client via a menu that opens by right-clicking on the Yarra icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Release of YarraServer and Client Package</title>
      <link>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/release_june19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yarra-framework.org/blog/release_june19/</guid>
      <description>New versions of the YarraServer and Yarra Client packages have been released.
Yarra Client 0.53 adds support for our YarraCloud service. Moreover, new software versions of the Siemens scanners are supported, including VB19B, VE11D, VE11E,VE12U, XA11A, and XA11B. To use the Yarra Client on scanners with the XA software line (MAGNETOM Vida and Sola), it is necessary to install software certificates. Please contact us to obtain these certificates.
YarraServer 0.97 has now been built using an Ubuntu 16.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
